Excuse me.
Shithead.
You shouldn't be here.
I know. Ask for at
least $1,000, okay?
I'll get as much
as I can. You hide.
His wife took his kid
and a couple of million,
and we won't get a thousand.
Shut up and stay hidden.
I told him I was coming alone.
Hey, Mr. Crisp.
How's it going?
You said you had information
about my family.
Yeah, yeah, I do.
Well, let's have it.
Well, it's going to cost you.
Like $1,000?
(SIGHING)
Okay, that's obviously
not my final offer.
750 would be fine.
I mean, more than fine.
Just tell me what you have, Danny,
and I'll take good care of you.
Okay.
That sounds fair.
I was doing a delivery for Corky last week
out of state, and I ran into your ex.
How'd she look?
She looked great, Mr. Crisp. Yeah.
She changed her hair and stuff, but
she looked like a million dollars.
In fact, she looked
like about $3 million.
Did she see you?
No. I was changing a tire,
and suddenly, there she was across the
street, taking her kid into this school.
My boy?
Looked great.
He looked very healthy.
It's a real nice, healthy
place where they're living.
It snows in winter there.
Danny,
where are they?
At the school where I saw them...
Astoria Elementary School.
That's...
It's in Astoria, Oregon.
All right.
Did you tell anyone else this?
No. No way.
Hey, I'm not stupid, Mr. Crisp.
(GUNSHOT)
You're not?
Danny.
Danny! No!
Danny!
Get up!
Don't you die on me!
I didn't kill him.
Was it Crisp?
I don't know.
I didn't see anything.
I was in a box over there...
What are you doing?
Hey, hey, hey!
Stop it! Don't do that!
Don't go anywhere.
Let me go!
No! Let me off of him!
I don't like what you've done.
I really don't like it.
It feels terrible, and
it looks dreadful.
MAN: I'm trying my best.
Maybe your best isn't good enough.
I'm back.
Oh, great. Well, that was fast.
It was easy.
I have some great, exciting,
wonderful news, Mother.
Oh, you always exaggerate, Cullen.
Everything is always
great, terrific.
So, what's so great?
I just found out where
they're hiding.
Are you serious?
You really know where he is?
Manicure, Mr. Crisp?
CRISP:
Oh, how could I say no to you?
Tell me.
What's happened?
Just let me handle
this myself, Mother.
I know what I'm doing.
Everything is under control.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
It's all right. I'm
a police officer.
Crisp, you're under arrest.
Put your hands on
your head and get up!
Kimble, not again!
Your hands!
They're up. When will
you leave me alone?
Drop the gun! Drop the gun!
Hey, I'm a police officer.
This is an arrest.
CRISP:
This man's crazy. Look at him.
He'll kill me. You're just
going to stand there?
OFFICER: Freeze!
I'm a cop!
I'm Detective John Kimble.
This man is under arrest.
I'm checking.
You can't just walk in here
and put a gun in my face.
I'm trying to get a manicure.
I have witnesses.
I have a witness, too.
It's murder one this time.
Now you're mine.
CINDY: The bastard
handcuffed me to a dead man!
A dead man!
Come on. Sit down.
Now, did Danny ever say what
Crisp's wife looked like?
No.
Did he ever say what name
she was using in Oregon?
He didn't say anything.
Look, I just want to go home.
PHOEBE: After the lineup, I'll drive
you home. I'll even buy you dinner.
I'll even cook you dinner.
I'm not doing any lineup, and there
ain't jack shit you can do about it!
I've been after Crisp for four years, and
she's letting my key witness walk away?
Kimble, sit down!
Sit down.
- Sit.
PHOEBE: Now listen to me.
He killed your boyfriend.
All you have to do is point your finger,
and we can put him away for 30 years.
He wasn't my boyfriend.
I hardly knew the guy.
(SIGHING)
I know you're in there.
I know what you want,
but you ain't getting it.
No lineup, no testimony.
So shove your handcuffs
up your ass!
Now let me out of here!
PHOEBE: Slow down!
Open it and let me out!
SALAZAR: O'Hara, meet Kimble.
Kimble's been on this a long time.
Hi.
Let me take care of Cindy.
She'll make Crisp. I guarantee it.
What are you going to do, handcuff her
to your car and take her for a ride?
I'm not going to offer
to cook her dinner.
Kimble, hold on a second. I...
Difficult man. Got
to get to know him.
Oh, I can't wait.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Aah!
(GIGGLING)
Hey, baby.
MAN: What you mean, "Hey, baby?"
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(GRUNTING)
(CRASHING)
Shit!
Oh, excuse me.
I forgot to introduce myself.
My name is John Kimble,
(COCKING)
And I love my car.
I'll keep an eye on it for you.
You got a beautiful ride.
Shit. Who does he think he is?
He's lucky I didn't kick his ass.
(CROWD CHATTERING)
(LOUD HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(THUDDING)
Open up.
You can't come in.
Thank you.
What the fuck?
(ALL YELLING)
JOHN: All right, party's over.
Everyone go home.
Next time, my place.
So who are you, man?
Shit!
I'm the party-pooper.
Hi, Cindy.
Do you mind if I sit down?
No. Sit down, man.
Oh, it's so nice to see you again.
What are you doing
here, you asshole?
Cindy, I don't like you
using foul language,
not a classy girl like you.
Don't you have
anything better to do?
You don't understand.
I have nothing else to do, and
I have nowhere else to go.
Why are you staring
at me like that?
I like you, Cindy.
I'm going to be around you a lot.
Days, nights, weekends, holidays.
No. No, you can't.
Yes, I can.
I'm going to hang out with you
until the end of time.
MAN:
All right, move it in. Let's go.
Step onto the numbers.
Face front.
Everybody, hands to your side.
That's the creep.
Who?
Number five. That's him.
Good. Very good.
Mr. Crisp, you will be remanded
into custody until your trial.
Bailiff, remove the prisoner.
Shh. Don't say anything. Just take it
easy. I'll take care of it. Trust me.
(WHISPERING) You know what to do?
I'm your mother, aren't I?
Mind if I talk to my
friend a little bit?
I'm not talking to anybody
without my lawyer.
He's right in here.
You give me the names of your
drug suppliers and distributors,
and I'll tell the judge what a
nice, cooperative killer you are.
You think the jury's
going to convict me
on the testimony of that junkie?
You could be right.
But what about your wife?
You remember her?
All that hard-earned drug
money she stole from you?
How much was it, $3 million?
I bet she would make a
much better witness.
Kimble, you've wasted
years chasing after me,
and what has it gotten you, hmm?
Nothing.
I'll be out in a week,
and you'll still be eating take-out
food in that dump you live in.
Yeah, I know all about you, Kimble.
Without me, you wouldn't
even have a life.
My old lady left
'cause of the money.
Yours left because she just
couldn't stand the sight of you.
I've never seen anyone
so little eat so much.
Yeah, I know. I'm hypoglycemic.
If I don't eat regularly,
I get a little nuts.
So, where you from?
Austria.
How long you been a cop?
I been a cop for 12 years.
My father was a cop,
my brother was a cop,
my mother was a cop's wife.
And I have no hobbies.
Good news.
You two are booked on the first
flight to Portland tomorrow.
Locate Crisp's wife and
offer her immunity
in exchange for her
testimony against him.
No offense to O'Hallahan,
but this is my case,
and I work alone.
He works alone. Not anymore.
She's going in undercover as a
substitute kindergarten teacher.
Not exactly a job for you.
I used to be a teacher.
We'll be fine.
What do I do?
She locates the kid, you find
the mother and the cash,
and Crisp spends his life
making license plates.
Bon voyage.
Oh, and Kimble, the name's O'Hara.
PHOEBE: Okay. Here's the wife
at 17. Real name's Rachel Myatt.
She's from Hannibal,
Missouri, class of '76.
Cheerleader, first violin
in the school orchestra,
captain of the girls'
softball team.
Her ambition was "To travel,
"experience life, and
meet interesting people."
Like Crisp.
Okay.
Relax.
Don't let him get to you.
That's her 10 years later.
It's a great shot of an ear.
You get in touch with her parents?
They're both dead.
The only relative she's
got left is the kid.
BOY: Hey.
Okay. This is the only
picture we have of him.
Cullen Jr., aged 3 months.
That helps much.
It's the best I could do.
Breakfast, sir? Ma'am?
- Please.
- No. No, no.
That's a first.
Listen, I was just thinking.
Maybe we should take a wild stab
at getting to know each other
before we have to
pretend we're married.
What do you want to know?
How long have we been married?
A long time.
People won't expect us to
talk much to each other.
BOY 1:
I want to read it, too. Stop it.
BOY 2: Please? Let me take a look.
Hey, come here.
If you don't stop screwing around back
there, this is what I'll do with you.
Ohh.
What's the matter?
I don't know.
I just don't feel so good.
You hungry?
I got to get out of here right now.
Get those tree stumps out of my
way before I vomit all over them.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
Is your wife okay, sir?
Compared to what?
PHOEBE: Maybe it was the burrito.
Or it could've been the sausages.
I don't think it was
the crab salad.
It couldn't have been the donuts.
(BURPS)
Excuse me.
Oh, I hate feeling like this.
I hate it, too.
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh what?
Uh-oh, pull over.
Now?
Yeah. Please hurry.
PHOEBE: The key! Give me the key!
Do you need a hand?
(VOMITING)
You okay?
I'm fine.
PHOEBE: I'll be fine.
Class starts at 9:00
in the morning.
I'll be fine.
You look much better already.
Oh. Kindergarten, 6-year-olds.
That's why I quit
teaching, you know.
I got so sick of
other people's kids.
I was afraid that I'd never
want to have any of my own.
I have a son.
He's 13.
I remember when he was 5.
He lives with his
mother and stepfather.
Aah!
What's the matter?
What... is... that?
Oh, excuse me. I forgot to
tell you. This is my ferret.
He doesn't bite. Don't worry.
(GASPING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Come on. Come on out.
This is all I need, an obstacle.
A goddamn obstacle.
He sends me an obstacle.
Here.
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
(DOOR SLAMMING)
Oh, God.
Don't worry.
I'm going to make it.
I just need a minute.
I'll be ready in just a minute.
I just got...
Oh, God.
How do I look?
(GASPING)
Take off the gun.
That's a good idea.
(CHUCKLES)
The little bastards are
going to eat you alive.
Get some rest, and don't worry.
I've been working
undercover for a long time.
They're 6-year-olds. How
much trouble can they be?
On second thought,
take the gun.
(TEACHER YELLING)
Matthew...
I sent you to the principal's
office because you punched Jenny.
I know. She poisoned your hamsters.
She told me all about it,
and she's very sorry.
And I'm sorry that I
didn't believe you.
- But you shouldn't punch people.
- MATTHEW: But she...
Mr. Kimble, Miss Schlowski
will see you now.
Let's go back to class.
Can I help you?
I'm John Kimble, your new
kindergarten teacher.
We were expecting a Miss O'Hara.
There's been a change of plan.
Four weeks into the new semester,
my superintendent told me I
had to replace Mrs. Hagley,
a kindergarten teacher
of 25 years' experience,
with an undercover police officer,
and he wouldn't even tell me why.
I don't suppose you would do me
the courtesy of filling me in.
I can't do that.
Oh. You can't do that.
I'm watching you.
All I have to do is tell my parents
that you're with the police,
and they'll yank their kids out of this
school so fast, we'd have to close.
And don't you think I won't if I
feel my children are in any danger.
They're not in danger.
I assume you have some
teaching experience.
They wouldn't have
sent me otherwise.
(CHILDREN SHOUTING)
Just wait here a minute.
(CHILDREN SHRIEKING)
Everybody sit down on the carpet!
Good morning, everyone.
ALL: Good morning, Miss Schlowski.
Your teacher, Mrs. Hagley, had
to go on an important trip.
Where'd she go?
That doesn't matter.
Did she die?
No, Lowell. She went
to see someone.
Did they die?
No, Lowell.
Everyone dies, you know.
MISS SCHLOWSKI: I know,
but not for a long, long time.
Now, until Mrs. Hagley comes back,
we have someone special to help.
This is Mr. Kimble, your
new kindergarten teacher.
Now, let's everybody say,
"Good morning, Mr. Kimble."
ALL: Good morning, Mr. Kimble.
Good morning.
They're all yours.
I'll be watching you.
Hi.
How are you?
I'm very happy to be here.
First, I would like to
just get to know you.
(SITS ON PIANO KEYS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
(SARCASTIC LAUGHING)
Quiet.
I'm going to ask you a
bunch of questions.
I want to have them
answered immediately.
How many of you were
born in Astoria?
Raise your hands. Let's see them.
Okay, hmm.
Now, anyone that was
not born in Astoria,
somewhere outside like
California, raise your hands.
(PANTING)
Yes.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Okay. You can go.
Boys have a penis.
Girls have a vagina.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Thanks for the tip.
Yes?
I need to go to the bathroom,
and I can't get these things off.
(SIGHING)
I'll get someone to help you.
I'll be right back, okay?
You've learned that the
"E" is often silent
when it immediately
follows another vowel.
Now write and say these words...
Oh, um...
Class, uh, Catherine,
can you take over for me, please?
Thank you.
CATHERINE: "E" is the fifth
letter of the alphabet.
Yes, can I help you?
I have a problem.
Mr. Kimble, I need to go real bad.
(CHUCKLES)
First day?
Yes.
I'll take care of her.
Thank you.
You know, kindergarten
is like the ocean.
Don't turn your back on it.
They're okay.
Don't worry. Everything
is under control.
(CHILDREN SCREAMING)
No.
Monsters.
What are you doing with this?
(CHILDREN YELLING)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
Aren't you going to break it up?
No. Two more days of
this, and he'll quit.
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up.
(PANTING)
(CHILDREN CRYING)
No. Don't start this.
Oh, no.
Aah!
(GASPING)
Attention!
This is your new class mascot.
What happened to your dog?
This is not a dog.
(FERRET WHIMPERING)
This is a ferret.
GIRL: What's a ferret?
That's a ferret.
CHILDREN: Oh!
If he bites you, you
get rabies and die.
No. That's not true.
He never bites.
Can I pet him?
Sure, but one at a time, okay?
Good. Okay, next one. Come on.
Yes.
Good. Yeah.
Good. Now we're having fun.
(BELL RINGS)
(CHILDREN YELLING)
What's that supposed to mean?
Mrs. Hagley is a lot
better than you.
Is she?
Is she really?
My mom's a teacher in this school,
and she's a lot
better than you, too.
Great.
On Monday nights, my mom tutors
and Mrs. Quinn takes care of me.
She's better than you, too.
Great.
And Frankie, my swimming teacher,
and Gus, my T-ball coach,
are better than you, too.
I really appreciate your honesty.
You happen to know someone
that's not better than me?
I don't know that many people.
John?
(GASPING)
Are you there?
How did it go?
Go away.
It went that well, huh?
You take over tomorrow.
And blow our cover?
Can't do it.
They're horrible.
Tell me about it.
WOMAN: He's gay. What kind of a man
teaches kindergarten? He's obviously gay.
A male kindergarten teacher
isn't what I'm used to.
Samantha calls him "The Giant."
There he is.
Where, honey?
Holy cow, is that your new teacher?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
- I'm not wearing makeup.
- None of us are.
You're married. You're
allowed to look like slobs.
Be good. I'll be
back to pick you up.
CHILDREN: Good morning, Mr. Kimble.
Good morning.
I told you he was big.
Play with the kids, honey.
Hi. I'm Jillian, Sylvester's mom.
Do you have a minute?
I'd like to speak with you.
Sure. Please.
Thank you.
A male kindergarten teacher.
That's unusual.
You're not from
around here, are you?
No. I'm not.
Neither am I.
Huh.
Anyway...
Um...
I have a small problem.
Yes?
You see, Sylvester's father
doesn't live with us anymore
and I've just been
worried about Sylvester.
He's been acting a
little strange lately.
You know, doing odd things.
Like what?
Well, it seems that's he's becoming a
little obsessed with playing with dolls.
You know, it's weird.
I think I can help you with that.
- Really?
- He uses the dolls to look up girls' skirts.
I caught him doing it yesterday.
Oh. Oh, well, that's a relief.
But I'll keep an eye on him, okay?
Thank you.
Does Sylvester ever see his father?
No. No, not since he was two.
His father lives in California.
That is far away.
Mmm-hmm.
Well, if you give me
his name and number,
I could talk to him about taking
more interest in his son.
That's very kind, but
I don't think so.
But it's tough on
Sylvester, don't you think?
No.
No, what's tough on Sylvester is his
father left us for another man.
Are you married, Mr. Kimble?
No, I'm not.
He's not married, Mom!
(SIGHING)
Welcome to Astoria,
the single-parent
capital of America.
Thank you for your time.
ALL:
I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America,
and to the republic for which it
stands, one nation under God,
indivisible
with liberty and justice for all.
Are these all your lunches?
You mean you eat other
people's lunches?
Stop it!
Now we're going to do
something extremely fun.
We're going to play a game called,
"Who is my daddy and
what does he do?"
Yes?
Is your daddy a fireman?
He's probably big.
Is he a wrestler?
A basketball coach?
No, no.
What's the matter?
I have a headache.
It might be a tumor.
It's not a tumor!
It's not a tumor at all.
(SIGHING)
What I meant was you tell me, who
is your daddy and what does he do?
ALL: Oh.
Get it?
We start right here. You.
My dad repairs cars driven
by women who are pinheads.
My dad doesn't do
anything since the crash.
My dad gives money to people
that doesn't have money,
and then people use that money,
then they give other money back
and they give the same amount
of money back to my dad.
My dad doesn't live
with us anymore.
He lives in New York
and drives a taxi.
My mom hopes he's going
to die real soon.
My dad watches TV all day long.
My dad works on computers,
and he's, um, the
boss of his company,
and, um, he has a
mustache and a beard.
JOHN: Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
(SIGHING)
He doesn't have that
much hair because...
And he... His head is so big
that he can't wear any hats.
My dad's divorced.
My mom's divorced.
My dad, um, is a psychologist,
and he helps people that are hurt or
lost their feelings, and, um, that's it.
BOTH: Our mom says that our
dad is a real sex machine.
Good.
I don't know what my dad does.
I haven't seen him in a long time.
He lives in France.
My dad is a gynecologist, and he
looks at vaginae all day long.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Thank you. Very good.
Okay. Next, uh...
What's his name with
his back to me?
His name's Zach Sullivan.
He doesn't like anyone
to talk to him.
He's a poo-poo head.
He's a poo-poo face.
BOY: He's a ca-ca poo-poo.
ALL: He's a poo-poo ca-ca.
Poo-poo ca-ca!
Quiet. That's enough.
Hey, Zach.
Did your daddy teach you this game?
Come on, Zach. Let's all play
together. It's so much more fun.
Leave me alone!
(FIRE ALARM RINGING)
What's that?
It's a fire alarm!
Come on, come on.
Everyone together! Come on.
I'm on fire!
JOHN: Come on. All together!
(ALARM RINGING)
Very straight. Very straight.
(CHILDREN SCREAMING)
JOHN:
Come on, come on. Get all together.
Everything together. Come on.
Come on. Quiet.
Quiet! Come on.
Shh! Quiet.
Well, we're all glad the
kindergarten class could join us.
(SNIGGERING)
That's four minutes. You should
be ashamed of yourselves.
All the other grades, your
times were an improvement,
but they're still not good enough.
I'm very disappointed.
All right, let's get
back into school.
(ALL CHATTERING)
Mrs. Sullivan!
PHOEBE: So the doctor
says it's a stomach flu.
I'm fine. I can eat
anything I want.
Let's find a restaurant.
Can we talk business?
There are 14 boys in the classroom.
So far I have three possible
suspects, one likely.
Here's a picture. You listening?
I'm listening.
His name's Zach Sullivan.
What do you think?
He's cute. Doesn't
anybody eat around here?
Listen, he's a dead
ringer for Crisp. Look.
Maybe. Come on, John. I'm hungry.
A table for two.
Thank you very much.
Two hot dogs.
Two hot dogs?
Mr. Kimble! Mr. Kimble!
Dominic.
It's him, Mom.
Joyce.
Hello, Joyce.
Dominic has been a great help.
He's a good kid.
Who's that?
JOHN: Who?
Her.
Oh, that? Uh, that is, uh...
(IN MOCK AUSTRIAN ACCENT)
I am his sister.
Oh, really? I wouldn't
have guessed.
You have to excuse my brother.
He has no manners.
My name is Ursula.
Wonderful to meet you.
I'm visiting here from Austria.
I'm Joyce Palmieri.
I work at John's school.
Ah.
And this is Dominic.
DOMINIC: Nice to meet you.
Would you like to
join us for dinner?
- No.
- Ja.
Ja.
Yes, of course.
That would be great.
Hi. There will be four of us.
WOMAN: Table 27.
Why did you tell her
you were my sister?
Relax, butch. The
love doctor is here.
Come to me. I want to start.
Okay. I want a rib eye steak with mashed
potatoes and a large green salad.
Oh, no. Wait a minute.
I want to start with the
spicy chicken wings.
Are they the tiny
ones without meat?
Actually, it's quite
a large serving.
Ah, good.
Ooh, good arms.
And a large bowl of
the clam chowder.
Uh, and the blueberry pie with
ice cream for dessert. Ja.
I like how they talk.
JOHN: I've been trying to get to know the
parents, but some of them are avoiding me.
Some of them are like that. It's a strange
town that way, especially with new arrivals.
What do you mean?
I think a lot of people
that come to small towns
are trying to get away from something,
or they're hiding something.
Like what?
Well, for example,
what brought you here?
Me? Well, there was an opening
for a kindergarten teacher.
Yeah, but what made you become a kindergarten
teacher? I mean, it is a bit unusual.
John is a bit unusual.
- Well...
- You are.
I was born in Austria. My father was
a teacher. My mother was a teacher.
So is Ursula.
Ja.
We have a tradition in Austria where we
follow the footsteps of our parents.
So, when I moved to this country,
I taught geography and
physical education in Arizona,
and then I coached basketball at an
all-girls school in Rhode Island, but
none of it made me really happy.
Why weren't you happy?
Ja. Why weren't you happy?
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I got tired of
teaching teenagers.
Because by the time they came to me, I felt
there wasn't much I could do with them.
I realized that the real
action is in kindergarten.
How long have you been
teaching kindergarten?
It's my second day.
Oh.
(GIGGLING)
(BURPING)
Ooh, excuse me, but
it's good. It is good.
Thanks again.
PHOEBE: Nice to meet you.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
(CHUCKLES)
I had a great time.
Ja, me, too.
Well, Kimble, I think you scored.
(CLICKING TONGUE)
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you talking about?
I'm only interested in her
because she works at the school.
She knows the children
and the parents.
If you were any stiffer,
we could take you surfing.
Now, I know you like that woman.
What is your problem?
The only problem I've got
is that I'm doing your job.
You should be cleaning up the paint and
reading stories about bears that go shopping.
I'm stuck with your job.
Yeah. You are.
That's right. I am.
Look, you're going to be
out of here in a few days.
You told me yourself you
had a few good leads.
You'll be back dealing with
junkies and murderers in no time.
(SIGHING)
They're pushing me around.
Who?
The kids.
They're walking all over me.
Listen, Kimble. You got to handle
this like any other police situation.
You walk into it showing
fear, you're dead,
and those kids know you're scared.
No fear.
JOHN: Today we're going
to play a new fun game.
It's called "police school."
I'm going to be your sheriff.
You're going to be
my deputy trainees.
(ALL GROANING)
Come on. Stop whining.
You kids are soft.
You lack discipline.
Well, I've got news for you.
You are mine now. You belong to me!
(GASPING)
You're not going to have your
mommies here to wipe your tushies.
Oh, no.
It's time to turn this
mush into muscles.
No more complaining. No more,
"I have to go to the bathroom."
There is no bathroom!
Now, the first thing the
deputy trainees have to learn
is to freeze whenever
you hear this.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Now, the next time you
hear this whistle,
each one of you get one toy.
How many?
ALL: One!
Good. Then bring it back
to the carpet, pronto.
Ready?
Wait for it.
(GIGGLING)
Sit down.
Ready?
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Go quickly. Get your toy.
Go. Go for it.
Yes. Very fast.
Good. Quickly. Bring the
toy back to the carpet.
Bring it back to the carpet.
Quick, quick, quick.
Back to the carpet.
Quickly.
Emma.
Emma, take your toy to the carpet.
I'm not a policeman.
I'm a princess.
Take your toy back to the carpet.
I'm not a policeman!
I'm a princess.
Take it back!
All right.
(CHILDREN CLAMORING)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Very good.
You did very well.
Now we're going to
play another game.
When you hear two whistle blows,
take your toy back where you got it
and come right back.
How many whistle blows?
ALL: Two!
Good. Ready?
(WHISTLE BLOWS TWICE)
Go.
Come on.
Come right back to the carpet.
Yes. It works. This is great.
Faster, faster. Come on. Yes. Come
back. Terrific. This is working. Wait.
I mean, you're very good deputies.
Your sheriff is proud of you.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
One, two, three, four.
ALL: One, two, three, four.
Wait! Take me.
Down. Up. Down.
Yes, yes, yes! You've got it.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Yes, Wanda. Good.
JOHN: Very good.
Big circles. Big circles. Good.
Now do the same thing. Way back.
And down in big circles. Big circles.
Yes.
(CHILDREN GIGGLING)
(BELL RINGING)
This is a fire drill!
This is a fire drill.
Run to the door.
Dominic, don't forget Ferret.
Yes. It's a fire drill. Come on.
Oh, this is terrible.
Come on. Come on.
JOHN: 29.
30.
31.
32.
33.
One more. Come on.
Down and up. Yes!
Yes! Zach is the winner.
Come on, you guys.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
JOHN: March, two, three, four.
March, two, three, four.
Swing your arms, two, three, four.
Swing them high. Two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
Wow.
ALL: One, two, three, four.
JOHN: Reading, writing, arithmetic.
ALL: Reading, writing, arithmetic!
Too much homework makes me sick.
ALL:
Too much homework makes me sick!
When it's time to pass the test...
ALL:
Kindergarten is the best.
ALL: Kindergarten is the best.
(CHEERING)
(ALL SINGING) E-I-E-I-O
And on that farm he had a duck
E-I-E-I-O
All right. Take your milk.
It makes you big and strong.
GIRL: It's story time, Mr. Kimble.
All right.
We all like this one and if you read us a
story now, everybody will go to sleep.
All right.
I used to read this to my son.
GIRL: What's his name?
Who?
Your son.
Oh, Alex is his name.
BOY: Where is he?
He lives with his mother.
You see, his mother
and I, we are...
Divorced. I know.
What's a divorce?
It's when your daddy lives someplace
else and comes over to take you places,
and your mommy says
he's a deadbeat.
No. It's when the daddy doesn't
want to see his little boy anymore.
That's not what it is.
Why don't you want to see
your little boy? Was he bad?
No, he was not bad.
It wasn't his fault at all.
You see, his mommy and
I, we just nev...
Just sit down, okay?
Let me just start reading.
Why don't you all lie down?
Okay.
Good. And rest.
"If you were a bird
and lived on high
"you'd lean on the wind
when the wind came by.
"You'd say to the wind
when it took you away,
"that's where I wanted to go today.
"Where am I going?
I don't quite know.
"What does it matter
where people go?
"Down to the wood where
the bluebells grow.
"Anywhere. Anywhere. I don't know."
(GASPING)
Hi.
I didn't mean to startle you.
(SIGHING)
I must have dozed off.
I can't believe you got
them all to sleep.
I worked them hard.
I was wondering if you'd like to come
to my place for dinner tomorrow night.
I would like that.
Yes.
Great. Well, here
are the directions.
How about 6:30, 7:00?
That would be fine.
(SIGHING)
What?
Um...
You... You've got a
little mustache.
Oh, it must be from the milk.
Well, I'd better get back to class.
I'll see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
(PHOEBE MOANING)
Freeze!
No!
No.
This is Henry Shoop, my fianc.
Hi.
Your fianc?
Yeah, my fianc.
Henry, this is obviously
my partner, John Kimble.
Oh, jeez. Uh...
- Hi.
- How you doing?
Let me get this,
and I'll be right out.
Oh!
It's okay, honey.
I'll be right out.
It's my birthday.
Well, congratulations.
Thanks. He came up here
just to surprise me.
And he made me my
favorite. Pasta a olio.
I love you, Henry.
I love you, too, Phoebes.
Uh... Well, I've got
to head back tonight.
I've got to work.
Henry's a chef.
I'm a chef.
You're marrying a chef?
I'm marrying a great chef.
That figures.
You mean that, a great chef?
Of course. You're a genius, Henry.
Not just a good chef?
Well, nice to meet you.
Congratulations. Happy birthday.
Thanks. You want some of this?
It wasn't overcooked?
You're the best.
It wasn't a little overcooked?
No. Al dente.
Zach.
Excuse me. I'm John
Kimble, Zach's teacher.
I didn't know he was following me.
Hi. I've been leaving
messages on your machine.
I'm sorry. Things have been hectic.
What about now?
Uh...
Go for a little walk. Your
teacher and I have to talk.
Uh...
I know what this is about.
I suppose you saw the
bruises on Zach's legs?
My husband has started
counseling about this.
He's been going for
three weeks now.
Please don't bring the school system
into it. It will make matters worse.
He's beating you, too?
(SIGHING)
If he wasn't going to counseling, I could
see the point of saying something.
But I'm sure there won't
be any more occurrences.
You won't say anything, will you?
Please?
If he does it again,
I press charges.
Zach.
(CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING)
You got the stuff?
Thanks, man.
Here, lady. I gave her your stuff.
Where's the rest of my money?
Who are you, old lady?
Your fairy godmother.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
JOHN: Come in.
Hi. It took all day, but I found out
Zach Sullivan and his mother...
- Aren't related to Crisp.
- I just found out.
Oh. I got a bottle of
wine for your big date...
It's not a date, I know.
But Joyce shouldn't think that.
Thanks. I don't think
it's a good idea.
Why not?
Quickest way to slip up
doing undercover work
is doing things you
normally wouldn't do.
Wait a minute.
You mean you wouldn't take wine to a
woman who's invited you for dinner?
Of course you would. And
flowers as well. Here you go.
She'll love them.
Well, here we are.
Wow. This is quite a place.
They must be paying you a lot
more than they're paying me.
I wish it was my house. It
belongs to a friend of mine.
After the divorce, he said we could stay
here in exchange for keeping the place up.
You must have nice friends.
Yes, I do.
Dinner won't be ready
for a few minutes.
Can you start a fire?
It shouldn't be a problem.
I'll show you where the wood is.
All right.
Come on. Come on!
Right here.
In here.
This is my secret hiding spot.
Wow. This is amazing.
I made it myself.
- What's this?
- Don't touch that!
It's a laser, and it'll burn
a hole right through you.
Okay. I'll be careful.
Oh, don't shoot.
Boom! Boom!
Don't shoot.
(CHUCKLING)
I put up these lasers
to protect us.
To protect you from what?
The bad people.
Do you want to see something else?
Come on.
What?
See that?
JOHN: You mean the tower?
I'm going to plant one of
my lasers on that antenna.
But I'll have to do it at night.
Otherwise the bad people
will know where it is.
Last one to the table
is a rotten banana!
JOYCE: Have you guys had fun?
- DOMINIC: Yeah.
- JOHN: Be right out!
What you doing in there?
(SIGHING)
I'm lost. Where is the dining
room? This house is huge.
Follow me, silly.
(SIGHING)
JOHN: These are beautiful
pictures of you and Dominic.
JOYCE: Thank you.
When I was putting Dominic to bed,
he mentioned you had a son, too.
That's right. But I'm divorced.
I'm lucky. My ex got remarried
to a very nice man.
He's really good to my son.
I see him a lot.
What about your ex-husband?
Does he see Dominic a lot?
Uh, no. After the divorce,
he moved back to France.
What about child
support and alimony?
Does he take care of you?
(CHUCKLES)
I'm sorry about being so personal.
(CLICKING TONGUE)
I was so glad to see him go I
didn't worry about that part.
Dominic doesn't even remember him.
I prefer it that way.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Why?
Well, Dominic was talking to me
about having to move around a lot
to keep the bad people away.
Bad people?
Something about having to leave
in the middle of the night
and leave his toys behind.
Oh, God.
I thought he'd
forgotten about that.
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to upset you.
It's not your fault.
The truth is, my ex-husband
is a walking nightmare.
He didn't leave us, we left him.
He found out where we were
and tried to kidnap Dominic.
He doesn't know where we are now,
and I'd like to keep it that way.
Of course. I'm glad he's in
France and doesn't live nearby.
He doesn't live in France.
I told Dominic that
he lived in France.
I didn't know who my ex-husband
was when I married him.
I was young and stupid,
and I made a mistake.
I don't want Dominic to pay for it.
(SIGHING)
Look, nobody around here
knows anything about this.
I can't even believe I told you.
You have to promise me
you won't tell anyone.
You can trust me.
JOHN: That's very good. Perfect.
Okay. Let's try it again.
Mary, you first.
Four scores and seven years ago.
ALL:
Our forefathers brought...
Four fathers?
Mr. Kimble, did Lincoln
have four fathers?
JOHN: Uh...
I had three fathers.
One named Walt, two named Ralph.
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
Did Lincoln have four mothers?
As a matter of fact,
he had two mothers.
Unfortunately, the first one died.
I knew it.
(GIRL GIGGLING)
Um... Okay.
Let's take a break. Come on.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
I want you to walk
around in a circle. Go.
Start. Come on.
Well, Joyce's story about
the house checked out.
It belongs to a guy who only
uses it during the ski season.
She's got under $1,000 in the
bank, no stocks, no bonds,
no other assets under the
name Joyce Palmieri.
Her teacher's salary is less
than mine, which is pathetic.
Keep looking. Check for offshore
accounts under Dominic's name...
She doesn't live like someone
with millions of dollars.
She doesn't even seem the type.
Kimble, this might not be her.
It's got to be her.
Why? Because she doesn't want to have
anything to do with her ex-husband?
I know it's her.
Know what I think?
You want it to be her.
You really like her,
and it's scaring you.
JILLIAN: Excuse me!
Surprise!
Ladies!
Ladies, surprise.
Obviously, I'm not
into baking cakes,
so I brought these little things
to donate for the raffle prizes.
(CHILDREN EXCLAIMING)
Who the hell is that?
JOHN: She's the one I
was telling you about.
Her husband ran away
with another guy.
It's been terrible for her.
You're not getting
mellow on me, are you?
Three, four.
- Hi.
- One, two, three...
Hi.
Come on. One, two, three, four.
Come on. Go, go.
I see they stuck you with the
Gettysburg Address this year.
They sure did.
Company, halt!
(CHILDREN GIGGLING)
Um...
About last night...
I've been thinking about it, and...
I'm glad I told you
all those things.
So am I.
Um, I... I better get going.
Yeah. I have to get going, too.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
See you tomorrow at the fair.
I'm looking forward to it.
What are you looking at?
(GIGGLING)
Shh!
March! One, two, three, four.
I was just talking to the
teacher, that's all.
Yeah. Don't laugh.
(ALL LAUGHING)
JOHN:
Okay. I'm proud of you. Keep going.
I'm sorry Zach's late.
The car wouldn't start.
You be a good boy. I love you.
Hi, champ.
Oh!
What's the matter?
Oh, no.
I fell down again.
Hey, wait a minute.
Uh...
I forgot to close the door to the
basement, and Zach had a bad fall.
The doctor says it's not
as bad as it looks.
You all say the same
thing, "He fell down."
Don't you have anything
better to say?
It's true!
I don't have to justify
myself to you!
You have no right talking
to me like that.
How are you doing?
You must be the Mr. Kimble
we hear so much about.
(GRUNTING)
You hit the kid, I hit you.
You bastard!
(GROANING)
You're not worth it.
I'm pressing charges against you.
Excuse me, everybody.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have hit the man,
especially in front of the children.
It was a mistake.
I checked you out.
There is no record of you ever
having taught at any public school,
in California or anywhere else.
Mr. Kimble, you have no teaching
experience whatsoever, do you?
Someone finally noticed.
I thought the introduction of
a ferret was a horrible idea,
but the children seemed to like it.
I thought the use of your police
whistle was outrageous...
That's all I could think of.
Please allow me to finish.
Sorry.
But it worked.
I have no idea what kind
of police officer you are,
but you're a very good teacher.
Thank you.
Now, will you tell me
something? Don't lie.
What did it feel like to
hit that son of a bitch?
It felt great.
Yeah.
Well, tomorrow morning.
Bright and early.
Thank you.
Yeah.
(SIGHING)
SALAZAR: Yeah, that's her.
And there goes our goddamn case.
Tell O'Hara and Kimble their witness
is dead, so Crisp is going to walk.
We want them back here.
We've got lots of
other cases to clear.
O'Hara says they think
they've located the wife.
And the money?
They're looking into it.
Bullshit.
Have them tell the wife we're letting
Crisp go, and he knows where she is.
If she wants police protection,
she'll produce the money.
Yes, sir.
Sorry it took so long, Cullen.
Hey, you're looking great.
I love you, Mother.
We're going to be a
family again, son.
(CLAMORING)
(CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Go!
(CROWD CLAPPING)
GIRL:
Fourscore and seven years ago...
ALL:
Our forefathers brought
forth on this continent...
ALL: Our forefathers brought
A new nation...
ALL: A new nation...
Conceived in liberty...
ALL: Conceived in liberty...
And dedicated to the proposition...
ALL:
That all men are created equal...
And that government...
ALL: And that government...
Of the people...
By the people...
And for the people...
ALL:
Shall not perish from this earth.
Thank you very much.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
(WHISTLING)
Oh!
I'd like to introduce you to
our kindergarten teacher.
He came to us as a
substitute teacher,
and he's proven to be
a wonderful asset.
Let's welcome him
into our community
and hope that he considers
staying on a permanent basis.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Mr. John Kimble.
(ALL CHEERING)
Nice town.
Hmm.
Ahh! Smell that fresh air.
We should think about
buying something up here,
like some log cabin in
the woods near a lake.
Kids love that outdoor
kind of stuff.
I'll be in the pharmacy.
Try not to step in anything.
MAN: I'd like to help you.
But we're pretty much out
of the race cars, unless...
This is the last one.
It's still in great shape.
If you don't mind
waiting, I'll wrap it up.
I'll knock 10% off...
I have a better idea.
I'll pay you twice
what he's charging.
I promised my boy I'd get him one.
I'd love to help you, but my kid's
been bugging me since Christmas.
I'll pay you four times
what it's worth.
Get your kid something even better.
Sorry. Can you gift-wrap it?
Hanna, could you wrap that, please?
No harm in trying.
Tourists.
(CHUCKLING)
(CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Great, Dominic. You're doing well.
I'll wait over here for you, okay?
Okay.
Great day, huh?
We've run out of time.
We've got to press Joyce now.
What do you mean?
Cindy O.D.'d last night.
Shit.
They released Crisp this morning.
He's probably on his way here.
Salazar told me to tell you this.
If Joyce is Crisp's wife,
she's got to cooperate
about the money,
or she gets no police protection.
Bastard.
Ursula, how are you?
What?
(SIGHING)
I've got to tell you the truth.
Her name's not Ursula.
She's not my sister.
I beg your pardon?
We're not who you think we are.
What is this?
We're police officers.
We know who you are...
Rachel.
This is a joke, right?
PHOEBE: No. This is no joke.
You took $3 million.
I think...
Crisp knows where you are.
He could be here any minute.
Where's Dominic?
You'll get immunity for your
testimony, but we need you to help us.
Where's Dominic?
On a pony.
We'll offer protection if you
tell us about the money.
There's no money,
you son of a bitch.
There never was!
No, it's not fair!
I'm not finished yet!
The bad people have found us.
What do you mean, "no money?"
Why are you mad at Mr. Kimble?
Because he's a jerk.
Leave me alone!
JOHN: Joyce, wait! Wait!
If you didn't take the
money, why is he after you?
He doesn't want me.
He wants Dominic.
She's going to run again.
Yeah.
Unless we do something about it.
Hey, snap out of it!
Daryl. Daryl.
I'm sorry. I wanted to
give you a second chance.
$200 cash.
What is wrong with you?
I'm still not getting through
to you, am I, Daryl?
(GRUNTING)
Mother, got this great
surprise for Junior.
That'll be $57.90.
$57.90.
Children's aspirin, children's
decongestant, antihistamine.
A thermometer?
A lot of flu going around, right?
It is the season.
The boy's not sick.
Doesn't hurt to take precautions.
Mother, you are going
to make him sick.
You stuffed all this crap into
me, and nothing was wrong.
That's why there was
nothing wrong with you.
Now, how can you argue with that?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Joyce!
Joyce! Dominic!
You bastard! Where's Dominic?
I don't know. What happened?
You led him here. If he has
Dominic, I'll kill you.
Let go of me!
We'll find him. Stop it.
We'll find him.
(SOBBING)
JOYCE: Dominic!
Did he say anything before he left?
He said something about
getting his lasers.
Lasers? I think I know where he is.
Aah! Help!
Help! Help!
DOMINIC: Somebody! Help!
Hold on!
I'll get him down.
Help!
Hold on. I'm right here.
Good boy.
All right. Just hold on.
Okay. Just hold on.
Oh, good. Okay.
I was going to put the
lasers in the antenna.
I know. Don't worry
about anything now.
I got you. Just hold on tight now.
Hold on tight, okay?
Good.
JOYCE: If I lost Dominic, I don't
think I could go on living.
You're not going to lose him.
That's right. I'm not.
Cullen said I stole his money so these
creeps would follow us for a reward.
You don't know what he's like.
Oh, yes, I do. I know him well.
That's why I don't want
him to get you two.
Can't trust you or anybody.
You can trust me.
That's what you said before.
And you turned out to be a cop.
I... I didn't mean to hurt you.
I wish I was a
kindergarten teacher,
but I'm not.
I'm a cop.
That's all I know how to be.
I have to get out of here.
You have a son.
If you were me, you'd
do the same thing.
I have a son I've hardly
seen in seven years.
I don't mean anything to him.
My ex-wife got remarried.
She doesn't want me
to be part of his life.
I lost my family.
(SIGHING)
I should never have let it happen.
Why are you telling me all of this?
I don't want to lose you.
I don't want to lose Dominic.
I swear you'll never have
to run from him again.
JOHN: Don't worry about anything, okay?
We're going to be right across the hall.
Everything's going to be fine.
We just want to be extra careful.
Thanks.
Don't worry.
(CHILDREN WHOOPING)
All right, all right. Settle down.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Good morning.
Good morning, Mr. Kimble.
Sit down.
It's very nice to
see you all again.
Meet my very good
friend, Phoebe O'Hara.
ALL: Good morning, Phoebe.
Miss O'Hara is going to talk to you
about something very important.
So pay attention to what
she has to say, okay?
Remember, no fear.
Thanks.
Yeah?
Boys have a penis.
Girls have a vagina.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Well, you taught them the basics.
That's important.
Okay, now, today
we're going to talk
about something else
that's really important.
Today we're going to
talk about strangers.
If a stranger knocks on your
door, never answer the door.
Because we never talk to strangers.
Let's say that together.
ALL: We never talk to strangers.
PHOEBE: Right.
Can we talk to kids?
Yeah, it's okay.
You can talk to kids.
What about dogs?
Huh?
Can we talk to dogs?
Yeah, you can talk to dogs.
But what you can't do,
what you must never ever do is...
ALL: Never talk to strangers.
MISS SCHLOWSKI:
On the kindergarten level,
we try to emphasize the three C's:
Caring, courtesy and courage.
Courage.
That's my philosophy, too.
Are you a single parent, Mr. Green?
No, my wife had to stay behind to
complete the sale of our home.
I'm checking the schools
before we buy a home here.
Most kindergarten
children can't read yet.
My son can.
He reads at 6? That's good.
And writes. I taught him myself.
He sounds like a special child.
CRISP: He is. He's a great athlete.
Here's what you've waited
for. The kindergarten.
Have a look.
(CHILDREN YELLING)
PHOEBE: Oh, Dominic, Dominic,
Dominic is king of the mountain!
Way to go, Dominic.
Here's your crown.
Congratulations, Dominic.
The king of Mount Kimble!
Dominic.
(CHILDREN CHEERING)
Ahh!
(JOHN LAUGHING)
He looks odd, but he's
a wonderful teacher.
Yes, I'm sure he is.
(CHUCKLES)
Did you see Cullen Jr.?
Yeah, yeah.
She calls him Dominic.
She'd always wanted
to name him Dominic.
What a dumb name.
Put that cigar out.
It's unhealthy for the kid.
PHOEBE: Then you make your
airplane go up into the clouds.
(FIRE ALARM RINGING)
Check it out.
Right.
JOHN: Okay, stay calm.
Okay, it's probably a fire drill.
Oh, man.
Kimble, the hallway's
full of smoke.
Okay, this is a fire drill.
Come on.
This is the real thing.
Just the way we practiced.
Go out there.
Fast. Just the way we practiced it.
(CHILDREN SCREAMING)
Come on.
PHOEBE: Come on.
It's only water. Don't be scared.
PHOEBE:
Stay close to the wall. Let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Dominic, stay close to me, okay?
Stay close to me.
(SIREN WAILING)
Stay behind me.
Don't get separated.
Aah!
(SOBBING)
Are you all right?
Come on. Let's go.
Dominic, wait!
Dominic!
Help! Somebody help me!
Help!
Stranger!
- Stranger!
JOHN: Dominic! Where's Dominic?
Dominic!
(SCREAMING)
Okay, stay together. Stay together.
Stay together. Hold
onto your partner.
Okay, don't lag behind.
Hold onto my hand.
Stay together.
Where's Dominic?
He's inside. Kimble's
looking for him.
Joyce!
Help!
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm not going to hurt you.
It's okay.
I'm a fireman.
I help people.
Well, where's your hat?
My hat?
I love this.
I can't fool my own boy.
He's just 6 years old.
You're right. I'm no jerk fireman.
I'm going to tell you
something, Dominic.
It's going to be hard
for you to understand,
but you got to believe me.
(BREATHING HEAVY)
I'm your father, Dominic.
Your father.
Don't you recognize me?
No.
Sure you do. It's me.
Don't you remember twinkle,
twinkle, little star?
We have the same kind of hands.
Don't you remember?
You're not my father.
My father lives in France.
Your mother told you that,
but that's not true!
I'm your father!
I've been searching for
you for five years.
Help! Help!
Dominic, I'm your father.
You're going to have to do what
I say. Do you understand?
Freeze!
(EXCLAIMING)
Don't you know there's a fire?
We thought it was another drill.
Well, get out!
Yes, sir.
Whoa, honey.
That's a fire in there.
I got a kid in there. I'm a cop.
If I need a ticket
fixed, I'll call you.
In the meantime, stay out. Go on.
All right.
(GASPING)
Quiet, you hear me? Quiet.
No!
Rachel!
Let go!
Just what I need.
Please, let him go.
Let him go!
How the hell do you
get out of here?
Please, please, don't do this!
You're scaring him!
Scared? Of course he's scared.
You told him lies about me.
My son doesn't know
me because of you.
Listen! Just listen.
You stole him from me!
Please, give him back.
Don't touch him!
(YELLING)
Dominic, I had to do it!
I didn't want to do it.
She made me.
Everything's going
to be okay, Dominic.
Dominic?
Come back.
We're getting out of here. Dominic?
Going to start a whole new family.
(SHRIEKING)
CRISP: Dominic!
Gotcha!
I love you. Do you understand?
Tell me you understand that.
Say it. Say it!
I understand.
Daddy.
Hold it! Right there.
Drop it! Hurry!
Don't. Don't.
He's not your hostage.
He's your son.
Drop it. On the floor.
You'll do this to your own son?
Drop it! I'm losing it! Hurry!
Relax. I'm putting it down.
Hurry!
Here it is. Here it is.
Just don't harm the boy, okay?
Good. Good. That's smart.
All right.
Why don't you let the boy go now?
The boy is mine!
He's my boy!
You get your own goddamn family!
(SCREAMING)
(GUN FIRING)
No!
(GROANING)
Are you okay?
I'm okay. Get Dominic.
Okay. Dominic!
Dominic!
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
Where's my grandson?
I don't know.
(GUN FIRING)
Where's my grandson?
Go to hell.
That's where you're going,
you son of a bitch!
(GRUNTING)
You're not so tough without
your car, are you?
Mr. Kimble, are you all right?
(SIREN WAILING)
Oh, I hate this.
Nah, he doesn't want to eat that.
He's a tough guy.
Tough guys don't eat Jell-O.
I'll come back later.
JOHN: Hi.
Hi. How you feeling?
Much better.
How about you?
I'll live.
Check out of here.
This stuff will kill you.
Just don't throw up on me.
I'm not going to throw up on
you, but I am going to kiss you.
Phoebe.
Thanks.
Thanks, partner.
Sure.
How's everybody feeling today?
I brought goodies. Did I do that?
Give me the flowers.
I got some goodies and...
I got it caught.
And something I cooked myself.
I almost didn't recognize you
with all your clothes on.
You look good yourself.
(SCREAMING)
HENRY: Did I... I'm sorry.
PHOEBE: The wedding.
Yeah. Uh...
You're coming to the
wedding, right?
Is it safe?
(CHUCKLING)
I wouldn't miss this for the world.
So...
Where do we send the invitation?
Hmm?
They're all yours.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Hi, kids.
Mr. Kimble!
I'm back.
(ALL CHEERING)
Didn't join the union until...
(CHILDREN CHEERING)
Class, excuse me.
(GIGGLING)
Uh-oh. They're going to do it.
(CHILDREN WHOOPING)